<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jeff Weber&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jeff Weber&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright notice</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a DNS Load Balancer</title>
      <link>/posts/building-a-dns-load-balancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/building-a-dns-load-balancer/</guid>
      <description>After my last post on things to consider with DNS based load balancing I had been thinking about that problem in more detail. In the work setting we replaced the custom solution I described with a new service offering based on one of the commercial GLB products. While it&amp;rsquo;s working without issues and removed some complexity from my life, I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about how I might be a GLB solution because why not right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Load Balancing</title>
      <link>/posts/global-load-balancing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/global-load-balancing/</guid>
      <description>When most people talk about Global Load Balancing they&amp;rsquo;re typically describing manipulating DNS records to allow traffic to flow to one of many similar instances of the same application for resiliency purposes. There are quite a few situations where this kind of configuration makes sense, but before implementing it you should be aware of the &amp;ldquo;gotchas&amp;rdquo; pain for your application. After spending quite a bit of time debugging the use of DNS based load balancing I thought I would do a write-up that will try to cover the lessons I learned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Lab Infrastructure</title>
      <link>/posts/home-lab-infrastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/home-lab-infrastructure/</guid>
      <description>The desire to have a minimal computing environment at home has always been strong. Early on I was a big fan of having some nice recently decommissioned rack mount servers in the basement. Eventually however all the heat, noise, and high electric bills got to me and I switched mostly to beefing up my desktop and using tools like vagrant and virtual box to scratch my lab itch.
When Windows 10 came out I decided to replace virtual box with the built-in Hyper-V functionality, and that&amp;rsquo;s when all my troubles started.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>